https://aloha-college.com/en/legal-faq/#1472531131859-8dd21fe3-9709

Music lessons
Aloha College Football Club (ACFC)
Aloha College Basketball Club (ACBC)
Details of Website Holder
In compliance with Law 34/2002, dated July 11, regarding the Services of the Society of Information and Electronic Commerce (LSSICE), the details of this website’s holder are below:
This website is property of:
FUNDACIÓN ALOHA COLLEGE, CIF G92430040, registered as an Educational Private Foundation on 25 June 2003, and published in B.O.J.A. y B.O.E. on 14 July 2003.
Address: Urb. El Ángel, Nueva Andalucía, 29660, Marbella (Málaga)
Telephone: (+34) 952 814 133
e-mail: communications@aloha-college.com
Website Content
This website aims to inform users about the services offered by FUNDACIÓN ALOHA COLLEGE. Additionally, the users who are duly registered can access the online communication platform for parents, pupils and staff, set up by the school.
Privacy Policy
In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations, we inform you that the personal data you provide us with will be processed by ALOHA COLLEGE, Responsible for Processing, registered at : Urb. El Ángel, Nueva Andalucía, 29660, Marbella (Málaga). CIF: G92430040. Tf. (+34) 952 814 133. Email: dataprotection@aloha-college.com. You can contact our Data Protection Officer by sending an email to the address indicated.
You may exercise the rights set out below by sending an e-mail to the above e-mail address or by letter to the above address.
Right of access to personal data: you may request information on whether we are processing your data and for what purpose.
Right to request the rectification of your data if they are incorrect or their deletion if they are no longer necessary for the purpose for which they were collected.
Right to request a restriction on the processing of your data.
Right to object to the processing of your data.
Right to the portability of data to a new Data Controller.
In the event that you consider that there has been a breach of your right to data protection, you may file a complaint with the Spanish Data Protection Agency (www.agpd.es)”.
The following outsourced services are available with which the corresponding Treatment Manager Contract has been signed:
Dining room management.
Photographic reports.
Prevention of occupational risks.
Labour consultancy.
CCTV system maintenance.
Surveillance and concierge services.
Web maintenance.
Travel agency.
The following is a list of the basic information that we provide in the data collection forms used by the centre, both in paper and digital format. The information concerning the Data Controller, contact details and procedure for exercising rights set out above shall apply in all cases.
Enrolment Form
Purpose and legal basis
The purpose of the treatment is to provide education to students. The legal basis for the processing of your data is the execution of this contract and the fulfillment of legal obligations that affect the File Manager.
If you have voluntarily provided us with information about your child’s health, we inform you that we will only consider it for the sole purpose of ensuring the safety of your child and providing them with the necessary care.
Addressees
The data of the students strictly necessary will be communicated to:
-The entity with which the school subscribes the compulsory school insurance, in order to guarantee its coverage, by legal obligation.
-The Department of Education and Science of the Regional Government of Andalusia, as well as the school transport company, by legal obligation.
-Transport company, for the fulfilment of the contract signed with the parents or guardians.
– The International Baccalaureate Organisation, Edexcel, Cambridge International Examinations and Cambridge Assessment for the fulfilment of the contract signed with the parents or guardians.
-Travel agencies and companies organizing activities and events.
International Transfers
The Manager uses applications from Google Inc. as part of the centre’s management systems, so that personal data may be stored on the company’s servers under the Privacy Shield.
Storage periods
The data collected will be kept as long as the contractual relationship remains in force and during the periods of limitation of liability in civil and tax matters. Information regarding the student will be kept for as long as the student remains enrolled and for ten years after the student leaves the school.
Summer School Registration Form
Purpose and legal basis
The purpose of the treatment is to provide our teaching services to students. The legal basis for the processing of your data is the execution of the contract and the fulfilment of legal obligations that affect the File Manager.
If you have voluntarily provided us with information about your child’s health, we inform you that we will only consider it for the sole purpose of ensuring the safety of your child and providing you with the necessary care.
Addressees
The data of the students strictly necessary will be communicated to:
-The entity with which the school subscribes the compulsory school insurance, in order to guarantee its coverage, by legal obligation.
-The Department of Education and Science of the Regional Government of Andalusia, as well as the school transport company, by legal obligation.
-Transport company, for the fulfilment of the contract signed with the parents or guardians.
-Travel agencies and companies organising activities and events.
International Transfers
The Manager uses applications from Google Inc. as part of the centre’s management systems, so that personal data may be stored on the company’s servers under the Privacy Shield.
Storage periods
The data collected will be kept as long as the contractual relationship remains in force and during the periods of limitation of liability in civil and tax matters. Information regarding the student will be kept for as long as the student remains enrolled and for 10 years after the student leaves the school.
Medical and Dietary Form
Purpose and legal basis
The purpose of the treatment is to ensure the health and safety of the students and to provide them with the necessary care. The legal basis for the processing of your data is the protection of the vital interest of the student body.
Addressees
Data will not be passed on to third parties, unless legally obliged to do so.
International Transfers
The Manager uses applications from Google Inc. as part of the centre’s management systems, so that personal data may be stored on the company’s servers under the Privacy Shield.
Storage periods
Information regarding the student body will be kept for as long as the student remains enrolled and for ten years after the student leaves the school.
Medication Administration Form
Purpose and legal basis
The purpose of the treatment is to ensure the health and safety of the students and to provide them with the necessary care. The legal basis for the processing of your data is the protection of the vital interest of the student.
Addressees
Data will not be passed on to third parties, unless legally obliged to do so.
International Transfers
The Manager uses applications from Google Inc. as part of the centre’s management systems, so that personal data may be stored on the company’s servers under the Privacy Shield.
Storage periods
Information regarding the student body will be kept for as long as the student remains enrolled and for ten years after the student leaves the school.
Database Form
Purpose and legal basis
The purpose of the treatment is to keep up-to-date information regarding the students and their parents or guardians. The legal basis for the processing of your data is the execution of the contract.
Addressees
Data will not be passed on to third parties, unless legally obliged to do so.
International Transfers
The Manager uses applications from Google Inc. as part of the centre’s management systems, so that personal data may be stored on the company’s servers under the Privacy Shield.
Storage periods
Information regarding the student body will be kept for as long as the student remains enrolled and for 10 years after the student leaves the school.
CEP Application Form
Purpose and legal basis
The purpose of the treatment is to manage the extracurricular activities attended by the students. The legal basis for the treatment of your data is the execution of the contract and the fulfilment of legal obligations that are managed by the processor.
In the event that you have voluntarily provided us with information regarding your child’s health, we inform you that we will take it into account solely for the purpose of safeguarding your child’s safety and providing him/her with the necessary attention.
Addressees
Student data will not be communicated to third parties unless legally obliged to do so.
Storage Periods
The data collected will be kept as long as the contractual relationship remains in force and during the periods of limitation of liability in civil and tax matters. Information regarding the student body will be kept for as long as the student remains enrolled and for 10 years after the student leaves the school.
Employment Application Form
Purpose and legal basis
The purpose of processing is to manage the personnel selection processes. The legal basis for the processing of your data is your consent.
Addressees
Data will not be passed on to third parties, unless legally obliged to do so.
International Transfers
The Manager uses applications from Google Inc. as part of the centre’s management systems, so that personal data may be stored on the company’s servers under the Privacy Shield.
Storage periods
The data collected will be kept for a maximum period of three years.
Employment contract
Purpose and legal basis
The purpose of the processing is to manage the employment relationship established with the staff. The legal basis for the processing of your data is compliance with the employment contract.
Addressees
Social Security, by legal obligation.
Bank for the payment of salaries in compliance with the contract.
International Transfers
The Manager uses applications from Google Inc. as part of the centre’s management systems, so that personal data may be stored on the company’s servers under the Privacy Shield.
Storage periods
The data collected will be kept for as long as you work at the centre and for up to ten years from the end of your employment contract.
Date of Privacy Policy: 25/05/2018
Cookies Policy
In compliance with Law 34/2002, dated July 11, regarding the services of the society of information and electronic commerce, Fundación Aloha College hereby informs its users about the use of third party and persistent cookies to improve service.
What are Cookies?
A cookie is a file that is downloaded to your computer to access certain websites. Among other things, cookies allow a website to store and retrieve information about the browsing habits of a user or his/her system, depending on the type of navigation, in order to provide a better service through the website.
What kind of cookies use this site and what are their purpose?
Analytical cookies:
Google Analytics (Google.com) and others (addtocalendar.com, .scorecardresearch.com, .sharethis.com)
These allow the person responsible for their cookies to monitor and analyse the user’s online behaviour. They are used to evaluate the activity of the website and to create profiles of the users’ browsing.
docs.google.com, fonts.googleapis.com, googleusercontent.com, gstatic.com, maps.googleapis.com, notifications.google.com, support.google.com
GAPS/ 1:juLVCczFwfAxhDyUDliu_gVCwBItKw:hYNw1pdMb2gJtlFA
m/ rB8en1oXMOJ6dxYPE56yAg==
58903a79e6acf57dbe839d3a4a7284bb
JCS_INENREF / JCS_INENTIM /PHPSESSID /SJECT1711 / _wpss_h_ / _wpss_p_ / cf7msm_check / ckon1711 / euCookie / pll_language
Allow, block or delete cookies
You can allow, block or delete cookies installed on your computer by configuring the browser options installed on your computer.
Disable cookies in Chrome:
https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=es
Disable cookies in Firefox:
http://support.mozilla.org/es/kb/impedir-que-los-sitios-web-guarden-sus-preferencia
Disable Cookies in Internet Explorer:
http://windows.microsoft.com/es-es/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies
Disable cookies in Safari:
https://support.apple.com/kb/PH17191?locale=es_ES&viewlocale=en_US
Links
In case of links to third party websites, we hereby inform the users that the terms and conditions of those websites will be applied.
Intellectual and Industrial Property
All the names, logos, services, contents, photographs, graphs, images, software, links and any other type of information which appears in this website are copyrighted and, therefore, cannot be copied, distributed, publically communicated, changed or modified without the expressed authorisation of its legitimate holder.
Changes
FUNDACIÓN ALOHA COLLEGE reserves the right to modify these Terms at any time if considered necessary. The user undertakes to check the content of this Legal Notice and the Privacy Policy as it can be modified without prior notice.
Ask a question
If you do not find the answer for your question, you can ask us by submitting it using form below:
I have read and accept the privacy policy
This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply
LEGAL CLAUSE FOR FORM REQUESTING APPLICATION INFORMATION
In accordance with General Data Protection Regulations, we inform you that the personal data you provide will be processed by ALOHA COLLEGE, registered at : El Ángel, Nueva Andalucía, 29660, Marbella (Málaga). CIF: G92430040. Tf. (+34) 952 814 133. Email: dataprotection@aloha-college.com. You can contact our Data Protection Officer by sending an email to the address indicated.
The purpose of processing the data requested in this form is to carry out the application procedure. The legal basis for processing of your data is your consent. The data marked with an asterisk * must be supplied in order to process your application.
The processor uses applications from Google Inc. and ManageBac LLC (“OpenApply”) as part of the school’s management system, therefore personal data may be stored on the servers of those companies under the Privacy Shield.
The data collected will not be relayed to third parties and will be kept as long as necessary to process your application and during the periods of limitation of liability.
You may exercise your rights of access, rectification, elimination, limits to processing, opposition and portability of your data, and your right not to be subject to decisions based only on the automated treatment of your data, by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address indicated above or by sending a letter to the address above.
In the event that you consider that there has been a breach of your right to data protection, you may file a complaint with the Spanish Data Protection Agency (www.agpd.es)
Go to our online inquiry form
×
LEYENDA LEGAL PARA SOLICITUD DE ADMISIÓN
De acuerdo con el Reglamento General de Protección de Datos, le informamos de que los datos personales que nos facilite serán tratados por FUNDACIÓN ALOHA COLLEGE, Responsable del Tratamiento con domicilio en : Urb. El Ángel, Nueva Andalucía, 29660, Marbella (Málaga). CIF: G92430040. Tf. (+34) 952 814 133. Email: dataprotection@aloha-college.com. Puede contactar con nuestra Delegada de Protección de Datos enviando un email a la dirección indicada.
La finalidad del tratamiento de los datos solicitados en este formulario es gestionar su solicitud de plaza. La base legal para el tratamiento de sus datos es su consentimiento. Los datos marcados con asterisco (*) son obligatorios para poder atender su solicitud.
El Responsable utiliza aplicaciones de Google Inc. y de ManageBac LLC (“OpenApply”) como parte de los sistemas de gestión del centro, por lo que los datos personales podrán alojarse en los servidores de dichas empresas al amparo del Escudo de Privacidad.
Los datos recabados no se cederán a terceros y serán conservados el tiempo necesario para atender su solicitud y durante el plazo de prescripción de responsabilidades legales.
Podrá ejercer los derechos de acceso, rectificación, supresión, limitación, oposición y portabilidad de sus datos, así como a no ser objeto de decisiones basadas únicamente en el tratamiento automatizado de sus datos, cuando procedan enviando un e-mail a la dirección de correo electrónico antes indicada o mediante carta dirigida a la dirección también expuesta anteriormente.
En caso de que considere que existe alguna vulneración de su derecho a la protección de datos por mi parte, puede presentar una reclamación ante la Agencia Española de Protección de Datos (www.agpd.es).
Aceptar y acceder al formulario
×
By continuing to use the site, you agree to the use of cookies. These third party cookies are not needed for navigation.
You can find out more about which cookies we are using or switch them off in settings.
Accept
Reject
Change cookie settings
Close GDPR Cookie Settings
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Cookie Policy
Powered by Aloha College  GDPR Cookie Compliance
Privacy Overview
Cookies on this website are used to personalize content and advertisements, provide social media features, and analyze traffic. These third party cookies are not needed for navigation.
Cookie information is stored in your browser and perform functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful.
By continuing to use the site, you agree to the use of cookies
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Strictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
Enable or Disable Cookies
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.
Cookie Policy
More information about our Cookie Policy
Enable All
Save Changes
